SUBHAJIT PAUL

REACT JS | FLUTTER | JAVA SPRING BOOT | FULL-STACK DEVELOPER



- +91-8016970670
- psubhajit14@gmail.com
- Newtown, Kolkata, West Bengal Pin -700157
- https://github.com/psubhajit14

SKILLS

- React JS
- Redux
- Flutter
- Javascript
- Java Spring Boot
- SQL server, PL/ SQL
- Unit Testing (Enzyme, JUnit)
- Problem-Solving
- Project Management Tools (JIRA, Git)
- Strong Communication

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY

BP Poddar Institute of Management And Technology

2016 - 2020 DGPA - 8.68

PROFILE

Full stack web developer with **2+ years** of experience in building data intensive web applications with **React JS** and **Spring Boot** with **SQL server**. I have built few **Flutter** project. I have in depth understanding of the complete SDLC with skills in **HTML5**, **CSS**, **Javascript**, **React JS**, **Redux**, **Web API**, **Java Spring Boot**, **Flutter**, **Dart JS**, **SQL**, **Git**.

EXPERIENCE

SPECIALIST PROGRAMMER (SP)

infosys. Limited FEB 2022 - Present

DIGITAL SPECIALIST ENGINEER (DSE)

infosys. Limited 2021 - 2022

SYSTEM ENGINEER SPECIALIST (SES)

infosys. Limited 2020 - 2021

RESPONSIBILITIES

- In Infosys I have worked for a automobile dept. client as a React and Spring Full-Stack Developer. In their internal application used for car pricing and configuration which works in different phases in the supply chain.
- I implemented different batch Job and UI Screen for generating report which helped client to reduce workflow also validate and process data correctly.

PROJECTS I HAVE WORKED ON

A music player app that uses local storage music files to play music.
 It has extensive features like: explore songs by album, use of playlist, background play. You can check the demo:
 https://github.com/psubhajit14/relaxation-app

To know more: https://bit.ly/3hN0vyQ